health-partners.org 2015-12-31

# Privacy Statement | Mercy Health Corporate

This privacy statement describes the information gathering and dissemination practices for the Mercy Health corporate website (www.Mercy.com). Please read this statement carefully. It may change from time to time without notice, so please check back regularly.

##  Information We Collect

The Mercy Health corporate website does not collect or disclose information that identifies or that can be used to identify you personally; nor do we make use of cookies. However, we do collect nonpersonal information for aggregate study so that we may assess the effectiveness of particular sections, pages and features of our website. Included among these types of nonpersonal information are the number of visits to specific pages and the length of those visits, as well as visitor IP addresses and browser information.

In order to use the Mercy Health corporate website's Contact Us e-mail form to request additional information, you will need to provide us with your name and e-mail address. Your name and e-mail address will not be provided to any third parties. We also do track the number of requests we have received for particular kinds of information via the Contact Us feature, which guides us in determining additional information we may want to make directly available on our website in the future.

In order to use the update notification registry feature provided in the Financial & Investor Information section of Mercy Health's corporate website, you will need to provide us with your e-mail address and additional contact information. The information you give us will not be provided to any third parties and will be used solely so that we may notify you by e-mail when quarterly updates are made to information in this section of our website.

The Mercy Health corporate website also allows you to submit an online resume in response to job openings at specific Mercy Health organizations that are posted on this website. By using this feature to submit your resume, you are automatically consenting to the reproduction, distribution, sharing and transmittal of your resume to the extent necessary to facilitate the normal hiring practices of the Mercy Health organization to which you have applied. We may share this information with any search firms we retain to help us fill positions.

The Mercy Health corporate website also provides links to pages on our regional websites that offer patients the opportunity to pay online for services received at specific facilities within our regions. Payment information submitted via these online bill payment features does not come directly to the Mercy Health corporate website. If you use our regions' online bill payment features, please read their privacy/security statements carefully.

##  Links to Other Websites

The Mercy Health corporate website contains links to other websites, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. The Mercy Health corporate website also links to the websites of Mercy Health's regions, and these regional websites post their own privacy policies, which differ from our own. If you visit our regions' websites, please read their privacy policies carefully.

##  Contacting This Website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the Mercy Health corporate website or your dealings with the Mercy Health corporate website, you can contact us by completing this form.
